One Two
一  二
One two three four
一  二  三  四
Dashing through the snow
冲出大风雪
In a one-horse open sleigh
身后雪橇响叮当
Over the fields we go
飞奔过田野
Laughing all the way
欢笑又歌唱
Ha-ha-ha
哈  哈  哈
Bells on bob tail ring
铃声响叮当
Making spirits bright
精神多欢畅
What fun it is to fly and sing
今晚滑雪多么快乐
A sleighing song tonight
听我把歌儿唱
Oh, jingle bells
噢  叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle all the way
铃儿响叮当
Hey Hey
嘿嘿
Oh, what fun it is to fly
自由飞翔多快乐
In a one-horse open sleigh
身后雪橇响叮当
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle all the way
铃儿响叮当
Hey Hey
嘿  嘿
Oh, what fun it is to ride
自在奔跑多快乐
In a one-horse open sleigh
谁来坐这雪橇上
Thought I'd grab some friends
找几个朋友
And take them for a ride
带她们去游逛
Not so sure what's up
不知为什么
As ponies run and hide
却纷纷躲又藏
Put Rarity in the back
让瑞瑞坐在后面
Right next to Pinkie Pie
紧挨着萍琪派
Better buckle up, my friends
大家扣好安全带
'Cause we're about to fly
我带你去飞翔
Oh, jingle bells
噢  叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle all the way
铃儿响叮当
Hey hey
嘿  嘿
Oh, what fun it is to fly
自由飞翔多快乐
In a one-horse open sleigh
朋友坐在雪橇上
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle all the way
铃儿响叮当
Hey Hey
嘿  嘿
Oh, what fun it is to ride
自在奔跑多快乐
In a one-horse open sleigh
还有谁来一起浪
Go grab Applejack
去拉上阿杰
Who's hiding in the barn
她躲藏在谷仓
Put her in the back
通通坐后面
And leave behind the farm
又飞奔出农场
Sky is clear and blue
天空多晴朗
And the wind is at our tails
鬃毛也随风飘荡
Ponies, hold on tight because
大家快点抓稳喽
We're 'bout to tip the scales
咱这就要转向
Tomorrow is Christmas morning
明天就是圣诞节
Tomorrow is Christmas day
全年就等这一天
And Santa's coming 'round the corner
圣诞老人即将要出现
And he's bringing presents
礼物琳琅满目
'Cause he's been filling up that
因为他装了满满
Filling up that Santa sleigh
装了满满一雪橇
We start speeding up
快马又加鞭
As colors start to show
拉出七色光芒
Streaming through our manes
流淌在鬃毛间
The higher up we go
直冲九霄云上
Even faster still
速度再加快
Faces fearing doom
别满脸慌张
What fun it is to fly and sing
边飞边唱多快乐
As we sonic rainboom
彩虹音爆登场
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle all the way
铃儿响叮当
Hey Hey
嘿  嘿
Oh, what fun it is to fly
自在飞翔多快乐
In a one-horse open sleigh
朋友坐在雪橇上
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle bells
叮叮当
Hey
嘿
Jingle all the way
铃儿响叮当
Hey Hey
嘿  嘿
Oh, what fun it is to ride
自由奔跑多快乐
In a one-horse open sleigh
我们启程去远方
翻译/校对/润色
Rogerdaily
背景图绘制
Luka
时间轴
BronyDee
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看